Hi. Does anybody here know anyone at TuneCore? Because I have a pro account, yet I'm waiting
several days for someone to respond to me. It states very clearly on the website that if you
have a pro account, you will get responded to within 24 hours. My album was flagged for basic
stuff that needed to be corrected, but then they said that my song, Let's Make Out, was explicit.
Let's make out, no small talk, and kick to colonization. Rub my booty and tell me that we're gonna get
free. No small talk, let's make out and lift up liberation. Caress my back, kiss my neck, there's
romance and revolution. Discover my desire, read up, pull up, spit knowledge you've acquired, I'm so
sapiosexual. That is a word that means someone who is sexually aroused by intellect. Lovers make the
best fighters. I've learned, I've heard. This heavy world is much lighter when you can exhale.
Is the explicitness in the room with us? So someone can connect me to someone at TuneCore so I could
actually speak to a human versus the virtual assistant and the random email that is not being
responded to. That would be super duper duper helpful because then I can get my music up for
you all to be able to listen to through the streaming accounts that you have to pay for.
In the meantime, in between time, head on over to amandadiva.bandcamp.com where you can support
independent artists directly and we actually get some monetary support for our music versus
the 25 cents a year that we get from streaming.